let's nail it down to some individual
stock recommendations Kali was saying
that it's more important to map out
what's going on with the broader markets
in light of that what's the stock
specific strategy I'll go with the
defensive strategy on the long side HL
remains to be a buy the stock has
already corrected more than 15% in the
last 3 4 months uh so expecting the
stock to get into a mild pickup at least
over the near term the uh would suest a
buy with a target of 2570 stop L at 2450
Mark and second would be buy an IC
lomard in fact many of the insurance
stocks are actually looking very
attractive many of these stocks are
purched at a breakout level for
themselves so this could be an
interesting turnaround uh EV for
insurance names picking up in ic Lombard
targets of 1440 stop L 1380 all right
let's find out what the strategy is when
it comes to NES NES your top bets so
being defensive we a sell and a buy both
from the large caps first is a sell on
Titan uh overbought in the near term
showing first signs of a possible top
out a six stop loss at 3300 Target price
of 3,000 second is a Buy on hero Moto
cop which has been trying to make a
multi-year breakout move uh has made a
strong base around that 2900 to 3,100
Mark lot of consolidation done tried to
make a move up saw a correction of the
markets could again go up higher from
here on a good risk reward stop loss at
3,100 Target price of
3400 okay thanks very much for running
us through all your top recommendations
let's